Resha Puspita Dewi

Jalan Cipamokolan 19 RT/RW 07/08 Bandung, 40292

WhatsApp: +6285624180916 • ☑ Email: reshapuspitadewi@gmail.com
 in linkedin.com/in/reshapuspita
 O github.com/renvelvet

Summary: Undergraduate Student in Information System and Technology major with internship experience as Web Developer. Currently enrolled in Mobile Application Development (Android) in Bangkit Academy 2021 and interested in IoT for Smart City Industry where skills, knowledge, and experience can be fused in a dynamic environment.

Skills

o Platform: Windows, Linux Ubuntu

o **Programming Languages:** Java, JavaScript, Kotlin, C++ o **Web Frontend Technologies:** ReactJS, Bootstrap, Bulma

o Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, Postgresql

o Embedded Engineering: ESP32

o Patterns & Practices: Object-Oriented Programming, Functional Programming

o Tools: Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ IDEA, Sublime Text, Arduino IDE, Figma, Fritzing

Experiences

Teknologi Bangun Indonesia

Remote

Part-Time Remote Junior Full Stack Developer

Oct 2020 - Oct 2020

- Assigned to handle cron job in serverless architecture

Loker Programmer

Front End Programmer Intern

August 2020 - Oct 2020

- Project based internship
- Slicing UI design provided by UI designer team
- Implement interactive website using React Js

ProBotDev Sdn Bhd

Scrum Master Intern

April 2019 - June 2019

- Manage team's boards using GitScrum
- Communicate with project owner
- Held daily stand up, sprint review, etc

Education

Institut Teknologi Bandung

Auguts 2017 - Present

Information System & Technology

Projects

Travelimo (API)Final Project Digital Talent Incubator (DTI) Program

December 2020

December 2020

Create API for travel app using Node Js and Express Framework. Handle CRUD, 'search' and 'booking' feature for 2 modules

Digitarian (Web App)

Impact Byte

Final Project Full Stack Web Bootcamp

August 2020

Web app similiar to Patreon with minimum feature using MERN stack. Role as front-end developer and team leader with 4 team members.

Training/Certifications

Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, and Traveloka

Mobile Developer (Android) Cohort

Feb 2021 - Present

Telkom Digital Talent Incubator (DTI)

Backend Developer Talent

Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

Impact Byte

^o Full Stack Web Graduate

June 2020 - August 2020